Guide to the James H. Karales photographs, 1953-2006 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Logging Series, 1958-1959, (7 boxes)
  - Logging Work Prints, 8x10, (22 folders; 30 prints)
    Of the 30 large work prints, 6 are duplicates. Typically there is only one image from each roll in this size, with a few exceptions.
    - Work prints, 8x10: roll numbers AE 1, 6, 7, 11-14, 17, 18, 22, 22, 27, 31, 32; WC/NE 116, 123, 126, 131, 140 (Box 7)
  - Logging Negatives, (97 negative folders)
    Approximately 350 negative strips in 70 folders representing film rolls AE 1-70, and 27 folders of large-format 8x10 negatives from various Job C267940 rolls. Negative folders are labeled with roll numbers.
    - Negatives: roll numbers 1-40 and 1A-10A (Box 7-8)
  - Logging Finished Prints
    Original titles supplied by library staff.
    - [Mess hall], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-052)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 6:3; GDC 2601
    - [Elevated shot of logger camp huts, work buses], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-053)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 7:6; GDC 2638
    - [Man walking along felled tree, machine hanging from winch behind], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-054)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 19:26; GDC 2600
      Same content as print RL-10017-P078 (16 x 20 inches).
    - [Man standing atop logging truck, power lines crisscrossing the sky], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-055)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 20:26; GDC 2597
    - [Logger leaping, axe in hand, from cut timber to truck bed], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-056)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 34:11; GDC 2586
    - [Boat corrals timber, mid-range shot], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-057)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 36:23; GDC 2610
    - [Bend in the river, marshalling logs, man steering log], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-058)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 36:30; GDC 2585
    - [Shot from boat, truck looses timber into river], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-059)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 37:9; GDC 2591
    - [Four men balance on timber in river], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-060)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 37:32; GDC 2611
    - [Digger drags three felled trees, deforested land in background], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-061)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 44:34; GDC 2636
    - [Aerial shot of timber truck on road, road sharply carving logged land], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-062)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 45:30; GDC 2612
      Same content as print RL-10017-P082 (16 x 20 inches).
    - [Aerial shot of timber truck on road, road sharply carving logged land], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-063)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 45:30; GDC 2637
      Copy of RL-10017-P062; same content as print RL-10017-P082 (16 x 20 inches).
    - [Logger left foreground, smiling into camera], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-064)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 45:31; GDC 2544
    - [Machine laying timber onto truck bed, mist through trees], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-065)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 48:7; GDC 2589
    - [Felled tree, chainsaw], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-066)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 48:27; GDC 2599
    - [Looking down river, long shot of logs lined up], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-067)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 61:22; GDC 2596
      Same content as print RL-10017-P079.
    - [Landscape shot, shadowed hills with rectangular buildings, mist behind], 1958-1959, (8.5 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-068)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1; GDC 2546
    - [Landscape shot, shadowed hills with rectangular buildings, mist behind], 1958-1959, (8.5 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-069)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1; GDC 2623
      Copy of RL-10017-P068.
    - [Shot of the back of a tractor, pine seedling in foreground], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-070)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1; GDC 2635
    - [Aerial shot of river], 1958-1959, (9 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-071)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1; GDC 2701
    - [Three men directing logs on river, motorboat in background], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-072)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 6 5:12; GDC 2590
    - [Three men directing logs on river, motorboat in background], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-073)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 6 5:12; GDC 2639
      Copy of RL-10017-P072.
    - [Inside logging machine cab, looking out through dirty windshield], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-074)
      Legacy identifiers: E 5:11; GDC 2584
    - [Boat corrals timber, short-range shot], 1958-1959, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 24, Image RL-10017-P-075)
      Legacy identifiers: E 39:30; GDC 2594
    - [Logger sits on huge felled tree], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-076)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 2:35
    - [Logging camp], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-077)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 7:6
    - [Man walking along felled tree], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-078)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 9:26
      Same content as print RL-10017-P054 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - [Looking down river, long shot of logs lined up], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-079)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 16:22
      Same content as print RL-10017-P067 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - [Processing timber in warehouse], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-080)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 25:31
    - [Truck loaded with timber, drives down curving road], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-081)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 28:22
    - [Aerial shot of timber truck on road], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-082)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 1 45:30
    - [Four peaks in mist], 1958-1959, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-083)
      Legacy identifiers: AE 6 30:5
- Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) Series, 1960-1961, (2 boxes)
  The Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee was organized in 1960 at Shaw University in Raleigh, North Carolina. Many (if not all) images were taken by Karales at a Passive Resistance Training in Atlanta, Georgia in 1960, for a Look magazine assignment. Images capture African American men and women participating in group training sessions, simulating arguments and giving or receiving feigned physical abuse; in some images there are white people present. The 20 large-format black-and-white prints are the only iamges in this series; there are no contact sheets or negatives.
  - SNCC Finished Prints
    Twenty black-and-white gelatin silver prints, ranging in size from 11x14 or 16x20 inches. All prints were acquired from the Gary Davis Gallery and are marked on the back with the donor's identifier; the prints are arranged in identifier order. Titles in brackets supplied by library staff.
    - [Three men in right frame talking with man in left frame], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-084)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2711
      Same content as print RL-10017-P096 (16 x 20 inches)
    - [Man in left foreground, hand on left side of face, man out of focus on right], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-085)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2712
      Same content as print RL-10017-P102 (16 x 20 inches)
    - [Woman holding hand against cheek, downcast], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-086)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2713
    - [Woman sitting in chair, two men move aggressively against her], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-087)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2714
    - [Man in right background, out of focus man left foreground], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-088)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2715
      Same content as print RL-10017-P097 (16 x 20 inches).
    - [Woman sitting in chair in right frame, two men move aggressively against her], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-089)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2716
    - [Man sitting backwards on chair, hands clasped atop the chair back, looking right], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-090)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2717
    - [Shot from behind man, looking onto another seated man], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-091)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2718
      Same content as print RL-10017-P103 (16 x 20 inches).
    - [Two men, two women, looking to right, hands supporting chin], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-092)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2719
      Same content as RL-10017-P095 (16 x 20 inches).
    - [Woman being slapped by man], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-093)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2720
    - [Woman seated, as man simulates beating man], circa 1960-1961, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-094)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2721
    - [Two men, two women, looking to right, hands supporting chin], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-095)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2751
      Same content as print RL-10017-P092 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - [Three men in right frame heatedly conversing with man in left frame], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-096)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2752
      Same content as print RL-10017-P084 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - [Man in focus right background, out of focus man left foreground], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-097)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2753
      Same content as print RL-10017-P088 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - [Man and woman in right frame, two men in left frame], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-098)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2754
    - [Woman eyes raised upwards to the right, hands clasped together], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-099)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2774
    - [Close-up of woman's face in left foreground, man out of focus behind], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-100)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2775
    - [Man and woman sitting, man on right with hands clasped before face, woman supports her chin with hand], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-101)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2776
    - [Man in right foreground of frame, hand on left side of face, man out of focus in the left frame], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-102)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2777
      Same content as RL-10017-P085 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - [Shot from behind man, looking onto another seated man], circa 1960-1961, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-103)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2783
      Same content as RL-10017-P091 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
- Martin Luther King, Jr. Series, 1962, (4 boxes)
  Taken by Karales as he traveled with King and his entourage to marches and speeches in various locations, the images depict King, his family, and civil rights movement participants, including Rosa Parks. One series of images feature King at home with Coretta Scott King and his children and convey a sense of casual intimacy. Images taken during civil rights protests capture King interacting with participants, and King and other individuals speaking at rallies and in churches.
  Series includes large black-and-white gelatin silver prints ranging in size from as well as contact sheets and work prints (5x7 and 8x10 inches); there are no negatives. Other civil rights movement materials are housed in the Civil Rights Series and the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) Series. These images were published in Look magazine. All prints are marked on back with the photographer's roll and frame number.
  - MLK Jr. Contact Sheets, (3 folders; 19 prints)
    The contact sheets bear Karales' markings, indicating images selected for proof prints or finished prints. Folders in boxes are marked with roll numbers.
    - Contact sheets: Job 1028, rolls 1-6; 8-16; 18-19; 21-22; and 24-26 (Box 9)
  - MLK Jr. Work Prints, 5x7 and 8x10, (30 folders; 87 prints)
    Contains 30 5x7 and 57 8x10 work prints. Numbers represent rolls and frames, and are marked on the backs of the prints. Folders in boxes are titled with the roll numbers housed within. There are 2 folders of duplicate sheets, one for each size.
    - Work prints, 5x7 and 8x10: Job 1028 roll numbers 1, 3-5, 7-22, 24-25, and 27-29, and duplicates (Box 9)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Finished Prints, (14 prints)
    Thirteen 11x14 inch and one 16x20 inch black-and-white gelatin silver prints, selected from several hundred frames taken by Karales while he traveled with King's entourage in Georgia and Alabama.
    - Rosa Parks, King, Birmingham, 1962, 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-104)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 1:15; GDC 2558
    - [Close-up of King], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-105)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 3:5; GDC 2541
    - [Head shot of King and another man at microphone], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-106)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 3:17; GDC 2649
    - [King walking through airport], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-107)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 4:5; GDC 2578
    - [King and little child on sofa], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-108)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 4:11; F-KAR.P08
    - [King speaking in front of organ], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-109)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:22; GDC 2557
    - [King speaking in front of organ, right arm outsretched], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-110)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:27; GDC 2556
    - [King speaking in front of organ], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-111)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:28; GDC 2559
    - [King speaking in front of organ], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-112)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:32; GDC 2664
    - [Panel of speakers, standing and clapping], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-113)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 11:18; GDC 2555
    - [King and other crossed arms, holding hands], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-114)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 11:26; GDC 2640
    - [Preacher right foreground, King and others clasping hands behind him], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-115)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 13:15; GDC 2676
    - [King sitting at table with Coretta Scott King], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-116)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 20:33; F-KAR.P09
      Print slightly creased on bottom corner, small stains on bottom edge.
    - [King writing on paper, girl to his right], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-117)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 21:6; GDC 2648
    - [King smiling in focus in background, Coretta soft focus foreground], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-118)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 21:17; GDC 2631
    - [Group of people standing, looking up], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-119)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 25:36; GDC 2574
    - [King in left of frame, Citzens Federal Savings in background, young man in right foreground], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-120)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 26:11; GDC 2543
    - [King lifting boy up over his head], 1962, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-121)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 29:32; GDC 2633
    - [King sits at table talking, daughter lifts cookie from plate], 1962, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-122)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 20:17
- Vietnam Series, 1963-1967, (14 boxes)
  On assignment with Look magazine from 1963 to 1967, Karales travelled to South Vietnam twice to cover U.S. Special Forces units and their role during the Vietnam War. Selected images from the thousands of frames shot by Karales were published in Look magazine, and were reproduced extensively for other publications. All of the prints are in black-and-white, but there is a large group of over 1100 color slides. There are also contact sheets and small work prints included in this series.
  Subjects in the images include: U.S. soldiers in Saigon, in combat, and at rest; daily interactions between American soldiers and Vietnamese civilians, including soldiers giving away candy, food, medical supplies, and other items; images of dead U.S. and Viet Cong; village scenes, including attacks on villages and subsequent relocation efforts; a Catholic chaplain's service; Vietnamese prison camps and hospitals; U.S. doctors in Vietnam; a Montagnard refugee camp; patrol scenes and other action in the field and on rivers; a delta rice and sugar cane factories, with workers in some images; schools and temples; and Saigon street scenes, often with U.S. soldiers buying goods or interacting with civilians. There are images of prominent figures such as Sam Castan (reporter for Look, who worked closely with Karales and died in Vietnam), D. Halberstam, Ray Hernandon, and General Westmoreland. There are also a few pictures of Karales.
  Some images bear titles assigned by Karales; titles in brackets supplied by library staff. Prints are often stamped on the back with a year. All prints are marked on back with the roll and frame number. NOTE: titles on archival folders were taken from original envelopes, but often refer only to a subset of images in that folder; for example, a folder marked "Construction" may in fact contain only five or six images of construction projects, with the rest being street and combat scenes.
  - Vietnam Contact Sheets, (35 folders; 250 prints)
    The 250 contact sheets include Karales' markings indicating images selected for proof prints or finished prints. In some cases there are individual frames cut from the original contact sheets. There do not appear to be duplicate sheets. Folders in boxes are marked with roll numbers.
    - Contact sheets: Job 1610, rolls 1-192 (with some gaps in roll numbers) and an unidentified roll; 1610 test roll; Job 2226, rolls 1-9; Job 2735, rolls 1-17; and prints marked B34870, B34856, B37929, and B37930 (Box 10)
  - Vietnam Work Prints, 8x10, (95 folders; 214 prints)
    - Work prints, 8x10: Job 1610, roll numbers 3-192 (with gaps in roll numbers); Job 2226, rolls 1 and 3; Job 2735, rolls 2-4, 10, and an unidentified roll (Box 11-13)
  - Vietnam Color Slides, (35 folders; 1188 slides)
    Original titles found on slide boxes and packets are retained on folders. Titles often refer to only a few of the images contained in the group of slides; other subjects are usually also present.
    - ( slides) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Buddhist temple, (4 slides) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Feb. 65, (14 slides) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 65 Feb. 26, (80 slides) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 65 Feb. 26, (66 slides) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 65 Feb. 26, (80 slides) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 65 Mar. 2, (80 slides) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 65 Mar. 2, (75 slides) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Helicopters and wounded, (75 slides) (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - U.S. dead (seems to only have one related shot, a casket in a hearse), (20 slides) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - American funeral, (21 slides) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Westmorland, (49 slides) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Vietnam 1964, (88 slides) (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Buddhist demonstration, (114 slides) (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Wounded, (29 slides) (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Helicopters, (3 slides) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hass Fuch dead, (34 slides) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - G.I., (34 slides) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - [Untitled], (1 slide) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Communism, (26 slides) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Construction, (26 slides) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - War '66, (27 slides) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Vietnamese scenes, (34 slides) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Vietnam street scenes, (16 slides) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bar in Saigon, (24 slides) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Goods on street - Saigon, (17 slides) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Flea market, (32 slides) (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Execution wall - main market, (30 slides) (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Ship workers -Saigon, (15 slides) (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Days in the trees [Various shots of people on the street and at work sites, almost all wearing hats], (11 slides) (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Rejects, (192 slides) (Box 14, Folder 16)
      The majority depict street scenes and construction sites, with about two dozen images taken at a military base and airport.
    - Field scenes, (32 slides) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - G.I. in Saigon, (14 slides) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam Negatives, (233 negative folders)
    Approximately negative strips in several hundred folders, representing thousands of images for Jobs 1610, 2226, and others. Some are large-format, but most are 35mm strips, approximately 5 to a folder (segregated by roll). Roll numbers are marked on the negative folders.
    - Negatives: Jobs 1610, rolls 1-192 and a test roll; 2226 1-9; 2226 with "B" roll codes; and 2735 with "B" codes (Box 15-18)
  - Vietnam Finished Prints
    Fourteen black-and-white gelatin silver prints selected from the thousands of images Karales took in during two trips to combat areas in Vietnam in the 1960s. A large series of color slides are also found in this series.
    - [Prison camp, branch barricade], 1963-1967, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-123)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 40:25; GDC 2568
      Same content as RL-10017-P129 (16 x 20 inches).
    - [Child draws in dirt, other children look on], 1963-1967, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-124)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 48:30; GDC 2569
    - [Close up of white-haired man], 1963-1967, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-125)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 49:21; GDC 2606
    - [Child in front of barbed wire fence, reaching out], 1963-1967, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-126)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 104:15; GDC 2607
    - [Soldier carries lifeless child in arms], 1963-1967, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-127)
      Legacy identifiers: B34856:19; GDC 2651
    - [Convoy truck filled with soldiers and Karales], 1963-1967, (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-128)
      Legacy identifiers: B37930: 21
    - [Prison camp, branch barricade], 1963-1967, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-129)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 40:25
      Same content as print RL-10017-P123 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - [In left frame, man carrying child on back, woman carrying child behind him], 1963-1967, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-130)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 43:30
    - [Boy riding an oxen down road], 1963-1967, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-131)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 45:31
    - [Young girl holds toddler in arms, baskets strewn around], 1963-1967, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-132)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 48:12
    - [Line of men waiting to board army helicopter], 1963-1967, (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-133)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 120:26; GDC 2600